<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
	<!-- Item template for copy-paste
	<entityname.fad_></entityname.fad_>
	<entitydescription.fad_></entitydescription.fad_>
	-->

	<!-- Cook job and clothes related stuff -->
	<skillname.cooking>Cooking</skillname.cooking>
	<skilldescription.cooking>Cooking skill.</skilldescription.cooking>
	<jobname.fad_cook>Cook</jobname.fad_cook>
	<jobdescription.fad_cook>Cooks, well, cook. A submarine needs food, and usually you want someone to be good at cooking doing that.</jobdescription.fad_cook>
	<entityname.cookclothes>Cook's Clothes</entityname.cookclothes>
	<entitydescription.cookclothes>Clean, white, mostly sterile clothes.</entitydescription.cookclothes>
	<entityname.cookhat>Cook's Hat</entityname.cookhat>
	<entitydescription.cookhat>A hat that signifies the ship cook, by right of looking ridiculous.</entitydescription.cookhat>

	<!-- UI -->
	<displayname.fad_waterrefill>Water Bottle (Refill)</displayname.fad_waterrefill>
	<displayname.fad_coffeerefill>Coffee (Refill)</displayname.fad_coffeerefill>

	<!-- Advanced items -->
	<entityname.fad_compatpill>Compatibility Pill</entityname.fad_compatpill>
	<entitydescription.fad_compatpill>Provides compatibility for mods that override the Human character. Should not be used if nothing's overriding Human. Adds +3 Hunger and +3 Thirst.</entitydescription.fad_compatpill>

	<!-- Agriculture stuff -->
	<entityname.fad_coffeebean>Coffee Bean</entityname.fad_coffeebean>
	<entitydescription.fad_coffeebean>A coffee bean genetically modified to survive better on Europa.</entitydescription.fad_coffeebean>

	<!-- Placeable objects -->
	<entityname.fad_smlcookingstation>Cooking Station</entityname.fad_smlcookingstation>
	<entitydescription.fad_smlcookingstation>A device for cooking food and making drinks.</entitydescription.fad_smlcookingstation>
	<entityname.fad_smlsmlcookingstation>Small Cooking Station</entityname.fad_smlsmlcookingstation>
	<entitydescription.fad_smlcookingstation>A device for cooking food and making drinks. Place with Aim+Use.</entitydescription.fad_smlcookingstation>

	<!-- Raw food -->
	<entityname.fad_crawlermeat>Raw Crawler Steak</entityname.fad_crawlermeat>
	<entitydescription.fad_crawlermeat>Slimy and smells quite bad. Doesn't look particularly edible currently, but its certainly very nutricious.</entitydescription.fad_crawlermeat>
	<entityname.fad_molochmeat>Raw Moloch Meat</entityname.fad_molochmeat>
	<entitydescription.fad_molochmeat>Meat harvested from a Moloch. Shouldn't be eaten raw, This nutricious fat resembles that of a earthly whale.</entitydescription.fad_molochmeat>

	<!-- Drinks -->
	<entityname.fad_waterbottle>Water Bottle</entityname.fad_waterbottle>
	<entitydescription.fad_waterbottle>Europan Spring branded water, brought to you by the people behind Crawler Cola. May not actually be spring water.</entitydescription.fad_waterbottle>
	<entityname.fad_coffee>Coffee</entityname.fad_coffee>
	<entitydescription.fad_coffee>A caffeine-filled drink with a legacy dating back centuries.</entitydescription.fad_coffee>
	<entityname.fad_beer>Beer</entityname.fad_beer>
	<entitydescription.fad_beer>By using of ethanol and fermentation, you obtain not only an alternative for clean water, but an reliable pall to sorrow and drunken for</entitydescription.fad_beer>
	<entityname.fad_saltdrink>Saltvine Juice</entityname.fad_saltdrink>
	<entitydescription.fad_saltdrink>Exceptionally salty, Its not very refreshing, but quite tasty and gassy bittersweet.</entitydescription.fad_saltdrink>

	<!-- Food -->
	<entityname.fad_rationbar>Ration Bar</entityname.fad_rationbar>
	<entitydescription.fad_rationbar>This ration consist most of hard tack, small biscuits and sweet, to provide the basic,cheap and cost efficient energy to carry your day</entitydescription.fad_rationbar>
	<entityname.fad_hqrationbar>Coalition Standard Ration Bar</entityname.fad_hqrationbar>
	<entitydescription.fad_hqrationbar>This ration uses the official coalition recipe, consists of a very strange set of licorice shaped stews and candy, from the look its confirmable that it just mimics the taste of meat, and its still very low in fat and essential protein, but its still quite tasty, specially the sweet ones, and will carry on with your basic nutrition and your day</entitydescription.fad_hqrationbar>
	<entityname.fad_baguette>Baguette</entityname.fad_baguette>
	<entitydescription.fad_baguette>An Europan reproduction of an Earth baguette, Its very repleneshing, Of course,Should not be consumed through any orifice other than the mouth.</entitydescription.fad_baguette>
	<entityname.fad_cookie>Cookie</entityname.fad_cookie>
	<entitydescription.fad_cookie>Ah, brittle,warm, sligly sweet cookie, Just like Grandma Mudraptor used to make, On earth, a common pasty firm butter like sweet acompanies the cookies, refining even more the flavour, it appears that commerical and scientific research effort to genetically modify the ingredients of that sweet compounds recipe made, very lucious.</entitydescription.fad_cookie>
	<entityname.fad_huskcaviar>Husk Egg Caviar</entityname.fad_huskcaviar>
	<entitydescription.fad_huskcaviar>Supposedly the high class of Europa eat these slimy platters of previously lethal husk eggs, make sure to eat it with a antibiotic as a side dish.</entitydescription.fad_huskcaviar>
	<entityname.fad_curry>Curry</entityname.fad_curry>
	<entitydescription.fad_curry>Unfortunately, the ingredients to create the original pasty earthly curry don't grow well on Europa, as it uses a special pasta, so instead this is made from a generic and syntetic variant from elastin plants, which gives it a certain chewy texture, it still takes greatly, Its very replenishing and fills up hunger and thirst.</entitydescription.fad_curry>
	<entityname.fad_mudraptorscramble>Mudraptor Scramble</entityname.fad_mudraptorscramble>
	<entitydescription.fad_mudraptorscramble>Boiled and smashed, this egg is an absolute barbeque, with scrapes of tender soft and chewy meat well spread whitin its gorgeous salty and seasoned melting water, its a powerhouse of nutricion.</entitydescription.fad_mudraptorscramble>
	<entityname.fad_crawlersteak>Cooked Crawler Steak</entityname.fad_crawlersteak>
	<entitydescription.fad_crawlersteak>This meat resembles nothing to what it previously did - it smells quite nice and looks delicious.</entitydescription.fad_crawlersteak>
	<entityname.fad_molochsushi>Moloch Sushi</entityname.fad_molochsushi>
	<entitydescription.fad_molochsushi>All around sushi's wisdom, europan speciality, Its would be absurdly tasty, if you weren't sick of it.</entitydescription.fad_molochsushi>
</infotexts>
